Predict the price of the Uber ride from a given pickup point to the agreed drop-off location. 
Perform following tasks: 
1. Pre-process the dataset. 
2. Identify outliers. 
3. Check the correlation.
4. Implement linear regression and random forest regression models. 
5. Evaluate the models and compare their respective scores like R2, RMSE, etc.

Dataset link: https://www.kaggle.com/datasets/yasserh/uber-fares-dataset
